<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<UpdateDescriptor>
	<version>0.3.0</version>
	<filename>SpazAIR.air</filename>
	<description>
		<![CDATA[
			<strong>These are the changes in the new version:</strong>
			<ul>
				<li>All timelines now retrieve all data, not just from last 24 hours (including DMs, @s, sent messages, followers/following lists)</li>
				<li>New theme: "Dumb Terminal." Works best on Windows with Bistream Vera Sans Mono or Iconsolata font; OS X has readable mono fonts by default</li>
				<li>New window behaviors: Minimize to systray (on by default), minimize when in background, restore when in foreground</li>
				<li>Added Native Shell Menus under OS X</li>
				<li>Added System Tray Icon in Windows w/ context menu</li>
				<li>Added Dock item menu</li>
				<li>User-defined CSS tweaks file now works again</li>
				<li>Tweets can now be "selected." Hit '@' (SHIFT+2) to send reply to selected tweet's user</li>
				<li>Prefs that require restart to be applied are now indicated</li>
				<li>Better descriptions of data retrieval errors; should properly determine if response timed out or if request limit is exceeded</li>
				<li>Fixed charcount to reset properly after successful send</li>
				<li>Added simple DOM context menus - currently allow user to copy URLs to clipboard</li>
				<li>Use '-khtml-user-select' to limit selectability of elements; should eliminate many problems with onlick operations</li>
				<li>Popup panels should work a bit better; center properly and drag more easily. Popup panels will be moved to modal windows soon</li>
				<li>Upgraded to jQuery 1.2.1</li>
				<li>Dumped Interface lib, added jQuery.UI lib</li>
				<li>Fixed size of protected post icon</li>
				<li>Lots of code cleanup and refactoring</li>
			</ul>
		 ]]>
	</description>
	<ui>
		<upgrade>
			<![CDATA[
				<div id="update-description">
				<h2>A new version ({version}) is available!</h2>
				
				<p>Do you want to install the new version now (Spaz will restart)?

				<form name="UpdateForm">
					<input type="button" id="SpazUpdate_update" value="Yes"/>
					<input type="button" id="SpazUpdate_cancel" value="No"/>
				</form>
				
				Alternately, download this update manually at <a onClick='openInBrowser("http://funkatron.com/getspaz")'>http://funkatron.com/getspaz</a>.
				
				<p>{description}</p>
				
				</div>
			]]>
		</upgrade>
		<downgrade>
			<![CDATA[
				The version installed on your machine is newer than the one online!
			]]>			
		</downgrade>
		<noupgrade>
			<![CDATA[
				There are no new versions available at this time!
			]]>		
		</noupgrade>
		<downloading>Downloading upgrade...</downloading>
	</ui>
</UpdateDescriptor>