<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<UpdateDescriptor>
	<version>0.3.6</version>
	<filename>SpazAIR.air</filename>
	<description>
		<![CDATA[
			<strong>These are the changes in the new version:</strong>
			<ul>
				<li>New mailing list for support and discussion: <a href="http://groups.google.com/group/spaz-users">Spaz-Users</a></li>
				<li>Spaz now requires AIR Beta 3</li>
				<li>Replies, direct messages, and standard timelines now combined into one. Keyboard shortcut to filter tweets (see help)</li>
				<li>Timelines now prepend new messages to top instead of wiping and reloading everything</li>
				<li>Highlighting of replies and direct messages in your timeline</li>
				<li>Tooltips will preview title of external link if possible</li>
				<li>Tooltips will show Twitter user info if user is not protected</li>
				<li>Wilhelm!</li>
				<li>Sent timeline now includes direct messages</li>
				<li>Network refresh minimum is now 3 minutes; default is 4 minutes. Can still force refreshes with keystroke or clicking/switching tabs</li>
				<li>Followers and Following sections removed until a more effective, useful implementation can be designed (was much less useful if exceeded 100 users)</li>
				<li>Lots of new keyboard commands, including keyboard shortcuts for Markdown formatting. See Help section (<strong>?</strong>) for full details</li>
				<li>Rewritten inline link parsing</li>
				<li>Tooltips now hide automatically after 8 seconds</li>
				<li>Markdown parser modified to remove support for headers (#)</li>
				<li>Markdown parser modified so underlines (_) no longer translate to &lt;em&gt; (interfered with posting code snippets)</li>
				<li>Root menu dropped from OS X (for now)</li>
				<li>Major code rewrites to data retrieval, timeline creation, and event handling</li>
			</ul>
		 ]]>
	</description>
	<ui>
		<upgrade>
			<![CDATA[
				<div id="update-description">
				<h2>A new version ({version}) is available!</h2>
				
				<p>Do you want to install the new version now (Spaz will restart)?

				<form name="UpdateForm">
					<input type="button" id="SpazUpdate_update" value="Yes"/>
					<input type="button" id="SpazUpdate_cancel" value="No"/>
				</form>
				
				Alternately, download this update manually at <a onClick='openInBrowser("http://funkatron.com/getspaz")'>http://funkatron.com/getspaz</a>.
				
				<p>{description}</p>
				
				</div>
			]]>
		</upgrade>
		<downgrade>
			<![CDATA[
				The version installed on your machine is newer than the one online!
			]]>			
		</downgrade>
		<noupgrade>
			<![CDATA[
				There are no new versions available at this time!
			]]>		
		</noupgrade>
		<downloading>Downloading upgrade...</downloading>
	</ui>
</UpdateDescriptor>