<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<UpdateDescriptor>
	<version>0.3.8.0</version>
	<filename>SpazAIR.air</filename>
	<description>
		<![CDATA[
			<strong>These are the changes in the new version:</strong>
			<h2>0.3.8 (2008-05-14)</h2>
			
			<strong>Note: Your preferences will be reset after installing this version. Yep, it sucks, sorry!</strong>
			
			<ul>
				<li>FEATURE: @username hinting/auto-completion. List of names built from main timeline/friends/followers lists (must be loaded first)</li>
				<li>FEATURE: Emoticon support (developed by Graeme Dunlop/@kibitzer)</li>
				<li>FEATURE: New user context menus allow messaging, following of *any* users that appear in timeline (including usernames that appear inside tweets)</li>
				<li>FEATURE: Shortcut maker now automatically detects links in clipboard; will auto-convert and insert into clipboard</li>
				<li>FEATURE: new friends and followers tabs. Currently only shows first 100; this will be improved in the near future</li>
				<li>FEATURE: new Main Menu available from [Spaz] header button; presets many items previously available only as keyboard shortcuts</li>
				<li>FEATURE: Debug mode now utilizes AIRIntrospector system; allows for much more powerful examination of DOM and AJAX calls</li>
				<li>FEATURE: Tweets are now marked as "read" when they are unselected (themes will need to be updated to support "read" CSS class)</li>
				<li>FEATURE: Proper user theme support; place themes in user storage directory's "userthemes"</li>
				<li>FEATURE: added pref for scroll-to-top on refresh</li>
				<li>FEATURE: added pref for checking for "test" versions when looking for updates</li>
				<li>FEATURE: Just-posted tweets are now added to timeline immediately</li>
				<li>FEATURE: Visual wilhelm excitement</li>
				<li>FEATURE: added "hidden" pref (no UI, must manually edit prefs file) to change source string sent to Twitter.</li>
				<li>FIX: keyboard shortcuts now work under Linux (thanks agolna)</li>
				<li>FIX: set max number of entries allowed in timeline; default is 200 (change manually in prefs file)</li>
				<li>FIX: obnoxious error modal than blocked UI dropped; now uses notification popup.</li>
				<li>FIX: clicking on a tab before appropriate amount of time has passed will not cause refresh (to avoid inadvertent request limit problems)</li>
				<li>FIX: shutdown sound now plays. Skipped if CMD+Q is used to shut down.</li>
				<li>FIX: all API actions now performed over HTTPS</li>
				<li>FIX: better inline URL parsing; fewer "false positives"</li>
				<li>FIX: suppressed error messages on empty responses; these can be caused if user has no DMs or Replies</li>
				<li>CHANGE: Popups now open in separate windows</li>
				<li>CHANGE: upgrade to jQuery 1.2.3</li>
				<li>CHANGE: jquery.enchant alpha added</li>
				<li>CHANGE: jquery.ui alpha added</li>
				<li>CHANGE: Debug mode now a proper pref, not triggered by presence of marker file</li>
				<li>CHANGE: Completely rewritten Preference system – <strong>you will need to reset your prefs (sorry!)</strong></li>
				<li>CHANGE: Completely rewritten Auto-updating system</li>
				<li>CHANGE: Completely removed/rewrote all code that used sandboxing/bridging systems. Spaz now works completely in the AIR application sandbox.</li>
				<li>CHANGE: Lots and lots of refactoring all over the place</li>
				<li>CHANGE: Tons of little bug fixes; read SVN logs and diff if you're really that interested 8)</li>
			</ul>
		 ]]>
	</description>
	<ui>
		<upgrade>
			<![CDATA[
				<div id="update-description">
				<h2>A new version ({version}) is available!</h2>
				
				<p>Do you want to install the new version now (Spaz will restart)?

				<form name="UpdateForm">
					<input type="button" id="SpazUpdate_update" value="Yes"/>
					<input type="button" id="SpazUpdate_cancel" value="No"/>
				</form>
				
				Alternately, download this update manually at <a onClick='openInBrowser("http://funkatron.com/getspaz")'>http://funkatron.com/getspaz</a>.
				
				<p>{description}</p>
				
				</div>
			]]>
		</upgrade>
		<downgrade>
			<![CDATA[
				The version installed on your machine is newer than the one online!
			]]>			
		</downgrade>
		<noupgrade>
			<![CDATA[
				There are no new versions available at this time!
			]]>		
		</noupgrade>
		<downloading>Downloading upgrade...</downloading>
	</ui>
</UpdateDescriptor>